I've never seen
Purple Vine in person.
Every time before selling a painting,
she would call me from a public phone,
asking me to pick up the painting
at the usual place.
The sixth building
of the 23rd staff compound of the chemical fiber factory
in the old town.
The adoption agreement of Sunshine Orphanage.
But why is the name of the adoptee missing?
[Broken heel.]
[Purple vine.]
Where is it?
Why is it missing?
Isn't Mr. Liu the chief designer of women's wear?
Why are you also the chief designer of women's wear?
Are you new here?
You don't even know me.
Let me tell you.
I'm the chief designer of women's wear appointed by the Old Madam.
My work
have won awards in Japan's
top designer art exhibitions.
Isn't that a fake award?
You...
Where's the sample of Dark Fairy Tale?
Why are you yelling?
You scared me.
A key was missing when I handed over the office keys.
You stole it, didn't you?
Oh,
don't just say anything.
Watch out.
I'll sue you for defamation.
I installed a camera in my office.
I took it.
So what?
Hmm.
Give it back to me.
Your designs
are garbage.
The princesses
definitely don't like them.
I've already
destroyed them.
Are you trying to complain to Zhou Jian?
I don't care
about the supervising work.
I've already told the former chairman.
This young master
doesn't even bother to deal with you.
You've done quite a thorough investigation.
Hmm.
Hello?
What?
What are you talking about?
Hello.
Young Master.
Well,
long time no see.
Who are you?
I...
Come to the company.
Why should I?
This isn't a request,
this is a threat!
Jiang Li, how dare you talk to me like that!
Oh, young master,
this is just a small matter,
don't...
Don't touch me!
Don't come any closer!
If you come any closer, I'll break your leg!
Hmph!
Jiang Li,
You'd better have something urgent.
He destroyed the initial draft of Dark Fairy Tale.
Hmph.
You should handle this yourself.
Oh, dear.
We are good sisters.
I was just
messing around with you.
Baby.
He's with the Old Lady.
I have something to do.
I'm leaving.
You two have a good talk.
Jenny.
Yes?
Take a long vacation.
What?
Young Master,
are you kidding me?
I told you not to touch me.
Hmph!
Are you done?
After your sister and Zhou Jian's wedding,
I'm moving into the Lu family.
Don't push your luck.
Are you threatening me?
It's just a fair exchange.
You first.
Pay 31.8 yuan.
Take it.
Thank you.
Why are you staring at me?
Is there a financial statement on my face?
I'm just thinking that
the life-saving favor
is paid back with a convenience store lunch box.
Because the lunch box is the most practical
and can fill me up.
You are the most special rich second generation I've ever seen.
Do you like Lu Xu?
I'd be crazy to like him.
Then why are you engaged to him?
You...
Do you really want to marry him?
For money.
For the property of the Lu family.
Am I direct enough?
You're lying.
Your eyes tell me.
You're not the kind of person
sell yourself for money.
You rich second-generation
are always so self-righteous.
Don't think that you know me well
just because you've met me twice.
I can't empathize with what you've been through,
and you can't empathize with what I've been through.
Sorry,
I'm done eating.
I'll leave first.
Let me give you a ride.
I'm driving.
If you need any help,
just let me know.
Favor is the hardest to repay.
A bento is enough.
Dad,
look at my new toy car.
Where did you get it?
Did mom buy it for you?
Uncle bought it.
Go play by yourself.
Daddy has work to do.
So busy?
Tell Mom
I won't be home for dinner tonight.
Uncle,
do you like the toy car?
I like it.
A child's growth
needs a father's company.
Mumu is my son.
I don't need you to teach me
how to get along with my son.
Come on, Mumu.
Daddy won't go out.
After dinner,
I'll watch Father and Son with you.
Okay.
By the way,
after your wedding,
Jiang Li will move in.
I'm going to marry her.
Congratulations.
Are you sure
about Jiang Li?
Don't move.
This wig is your talisman.
If Jiang Li
really makes Zhou Jian divorce Lu Qianqian...
And then?
what are you going to do?
Will you abandon me?
In a couple of days,
Jiang Li will move into the Lu Family's old house.
At that time,
you help me keep an eye on her.
Keep her away from my sister.
Aren't you afraid
Jiang Li will lose control?
Here are President Zhou's recent spending records.
Can I ask you a question?
It depends on what the question is.
What's your purpose
in the Lu Family?